A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1960-1961
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1960-1961
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.641 II
This collection consists of 14,400 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was forwarded to the library on 5 August 1964.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
Contents List
- General Files, 1960-1961
  - "A - Am" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - "An - Az" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Admissions 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Air Force 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Airport 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Invitations not accepted 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Atlanta Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Baltimore Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Charleston, West Virginia Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Long Island, New York Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Lynchburg Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Peninsula Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Philadelphia Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Staunton Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Washington Club (University of Virginia Club of Washington) 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni - Wilmington Delaware Chapter 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Fund 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - American Association of University Professors 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - American Council on Education 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Annual Reports 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "A" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "B" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "C" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "D" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "E" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "F" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "G" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "H" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "I" (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "J" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "K" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "L" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "M" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "N" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "O" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "P" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "Q" (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "R" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "S" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "T" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "U" (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "V" (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "W" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Applications for Positions - "X - Y - Z" 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Architecture 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Army 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Army - R.O.T.C. 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Army - Judge Advocate General's (J.A.G.) School 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Art 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Art Commission 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Association of American Colleges 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Association of American Universities 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Astronomy 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Athletics 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Athletics - Report of Receipts and Disbursements 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Athletics - Atlantic Coast Conference 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Bill Elias 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Invitations to Board of Visitors 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: V.M.I. Game, 15 October 1960 (High School Senior Day) 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: Wake Forest Game, 29 October 1960 (Homecoming) 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: Maryland Game, 19 November 1960 (Band Day) 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football: University of North Carolina Game, 26 November 1960 (Commonwealth Day) 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - N.C.A.A. 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - General 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Athletics - Football 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Attorney General 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 4)
  - "Ba - Bl" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - "Bm - Bz" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Biology 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Blandy Farm 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Boatwright, John B., Jr. (see Legislative Program) 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Buildings and Grounds 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Atomic Reactor, 1959-1960 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Clinch Valley College 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Contracts, 1959 (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Copeley Hill 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Engineering Building (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Field House 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - George Mason College 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Law School Building, 1959 (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Life Science Building 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Medical Buildings 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Northern Virginia College (see George Mason College) 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Piedmont 1959 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Power Plant and Heating Mains, 1959 (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Building Program - Student Activities Building, 1959 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Bureau of Population and Economic Research 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Bureau of Public Administration 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Bursar 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Byrd, Senator Harry Flood 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Business Administration, Graduate School of (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - "Ca - Ck" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - "Cl - Ca" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Calendar for Deans 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Calendar of Events 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Carnegie Foundation 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Cavalier Daily 1960 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Chancellor 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Chemistry 1960-1961 (Box 6)
  - Classics 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - Clinch Valley College 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - Clippings 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, January - April 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, May - June 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, July - December 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - Commerce, McIntire Undergraduate School 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Commission on State Capital Outlays and Means of Financing 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Commissions, Studies, etc. (see Legislative Program) (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Administrative 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Academic Costume (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Academic Policy (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Admissions 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Arboretum Advisory 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Architectural Advisory 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Athletic 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Calendar 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Calendar of Events 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Catalogue 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Cemetery (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Cemetery Upkeep (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Chapel (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Chemistry Building 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Chemistry Department 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Clinch Valley College Advisory 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Clinch Valley College Building (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Clinch Valley Science Building 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Community Colleges 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Computation Center 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Contractual Relations 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Dormitories 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Dormitory Counselors (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Engineering Advisory (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Engineering Building (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Field House 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Fraternity 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Fulbright Awards 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Housing 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Isotope 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Lectures 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Life Science Building Plan (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Long Range Planning 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Orientation 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Personnel Policy 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Processions 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Public Occasions 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Public Relations 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Retirement (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Scholarships, Loans, and Employment 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Student Activities 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Student Financial Aid (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Student Union 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Tree 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Undergraduates 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Virginia Status of University Students 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Committee - Wilson Gee Institute for Research in the Social Sciences 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Comptroller 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - Cooper, Weldon 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - Copeley Hill (see also Building Program) 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - Council of Southern Universities (see also Southern Fellowships) 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - "D" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - Darden, Mr. C. W. 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - Dean of the University (see Student Affairs) (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - "E" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Economics 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Education 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Endowment - Contingent Fund 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Endowment Fund 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Engineering 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - English 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Enrollment 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Extension Division 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Extension Division - Northern Virginia Branch (see George Mason College of U.Va.) (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Extension Division - Richmond Branch 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Extension Division - Southwest Virginia 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Educational Communication Center 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Graphic Production Report to the President 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Faculty 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Faulkner Foundation 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - General 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Fulbright 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Rhodes 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Finals 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Ford Foundation (see Thomas Jefferson Center and Economics) 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Foreign Affairs 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Forestry (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Founder's Day 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Fraternities 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Fraternity - Chi Psi 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Fund for Adult Education 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - "G" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - General Assembly (see also Political File and Legislative Program) 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Geology 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Geography 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Gifts and Grants 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - George Mason College 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Germanic Languages and Russian 1960-1961 (Box 12)
  - Governor's Office 1960-1961 (Box 13)
  - Governor's Office - Advices of Allotment 1960-1961 (Box 13)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1960-1961 (Box 13)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration 1960-1961 (Box 13)
  - "Ha - Hk" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - "Hm - Hz" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Hall of Fame 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Highway Department 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - History 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Honor Committee 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Honors Courses 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Hospital 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Hospital - Medical Board of the Hospital 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Hospital - Statistical Reports of Hospital 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Hospital - Operating Budget 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Housing (see also Committee on University Housing) 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Human Events - publication 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Inauguration 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Institute of International Education 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "A" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "B" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "C" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "D" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "E" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "F" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "G" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "H" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "I" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "J" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "K" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "L" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "M" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "N" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "O" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "P" 1960-1961 (Box 15)
  - Invitations - "R" 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "S" 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "T" 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "U" 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "V" 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "W" 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Invitations - "X - Y - Z" 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Award (see McConnell Award) 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Center (see Economics and Ford Foundation) 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Memorial Foundation 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson, Thomas - Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Jefferson Society 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Law School 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Lectures - General 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Legal Matters 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Legislative Program 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Library 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Library - Board of Alderman 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Loan Funds 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - McConnell Award (see Thomas Jefferson Award) 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - McConnell Foundation 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - "Ma - Me" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - "Mi - Mz" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 17)
  - Madison Papers 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Mary Washington College - Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Mary Washington College - Dr. Simpson, Chancellor 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Maxwell Air Force Base 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Medicine 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Music 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - "N" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - National Association of State Universities 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - National Commission on Accrediting 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - National Damage Assessment Center 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - national Defense Education Act 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - National Science Foundation 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Naval R.O.T.C. 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Newcomb Hall 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Newsletter 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Nursing School 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - Nursing School - Report of Visit for Accreditation Purposes 1960-1961 (Box 18)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Old Dominion Foundation 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - "Pa - Pe" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - "Pf - Pz" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Personnel 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Philosophy 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Physics 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Political Science 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Possible Donors 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Public Relations (see Information Service) 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Presidents' Council 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Provost (see Chancellor, 1 June) 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Psychology 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Public Occasions (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Purchasing 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Questionnaires 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Radio 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Raven Society 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Recommendations 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Registrar 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Religion 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Remington Rand 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Requisitions 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Research 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Romance Languages 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - "Sa - Sl" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - "Sm - Sz" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Salaries 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Senate 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Seven Society 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Sociology 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Southern Fellowships Fund, The (see also Council of Southern Universities) 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Southern University Conference 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Southern Universities (see Council of Southern Universities) (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Space Study (folder empty) 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Speeches and Articles 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Speech and Drama 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - State Board of Education 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - State Department of Education 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - State Universities Association 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Statistics 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Student Affairs 1960-1961 (Box 22)
  - Student Aid Office 1960-1961 (Box 22)
  - Student Council 1960-1961 (Box 22)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - Travel 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - Treasurer of Virginia 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - United Nations 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - U. S. Department of State 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - University Center in Virginia 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - University Houses 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - University News Service 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - University Press 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - University of Virginia Weekly Bulletin 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - Visitors - Dockets and Minutes, January - June 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - General, January - June 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - General, July - December 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Berkeley, Mr. Norborne 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Blanton, Mr. T. H. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Bryan, Judge A. V. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Coxe, Mr. Whitwell W. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Fenwick, Mr. C. R. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Grear, Mr. F. B. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Hartfield, Mr. Joseph 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Jones, Mrs. B. T. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Lantor, Mrs. Nathan 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - McWane, Mr. Henry 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Martin, Dr. Walter B. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Montague, Mr. E. S. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Paschall, Mr. Davis Y. 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Visitors - Pollock, Mr. Herbert 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - "Wa - Wh" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 25)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 25)
  - WINA Radio Station 1960-1961 (Box 25)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1960-1961 (Box 25)
  - Wilson, Woodrow 1960-1961 (Box 25)
  - Women, Dean of 1960-1961 (Box 25)
  - Wright-Patterson Air Force Base (Annual College Representatives Conference) 1960-1961 (Box 25)
  - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box 25)